Guide to the Montana State Prison records 1864-1974
Montana Historical Society
- Montana State Prison
  - Prisoner Records
    - Prisoner description cards: Joe Miller, Joe Miller (alias Joe Corbin), Joe Miller, John Miller, John C. Miller, John David Miller (alias P.H. Pierce), John W. Miller, Joseph Miller, Larry E. Miller, Lester Miller, Lewis Miller, Marvin Miller, Max Miller, Merrill Miller, Paul Miller, R.F. Miller, Robert M. Miller, Roy Miller, Rudolph Miller, Scottie Miller, Scotty E. Miller, Solomon Miller, Stanley D. Miller, Thomas Miller, Victor Miller, William Miller, William T. Miller, A. X. Millier, Charles L. Milligan, Louis Milliken, Charles Mills, Donald E. Mills, Ed Mills, Frank Mills, George Mills, Harold Mills, Hugh Mills, Mark Mills, Paul Mills, Peter Mills, Ralph Mills, Richard Mills, W.H. Mills, John Millsap, Gabor Milot, Howard Milsten, Eugene Milton, L.E. Miner, Marvin Miner, Dallas L. Ming, Peter Minish, Peter H. Minish, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 29/3)
    - Prisoner description cards: Ernest Minor, James Minor, Willie B. Minter, Aldolpho Miranda, Steve Miross, Leo Misbach, Earl G. Mischke, C.H. Mishler, R.E. Mishler, Andrew Miskovich, Harvey Mitchel, Charles Mitchell, Clarence Wesley Mitchell, Donald Mitchell, Edward Mitchell, F.J. Mitchell, Harold B. Mitchell, Harry Mitchell, Harry Mitchell (True name is William James), Harry L. Mitchell, Henry Mitchell, John Mitchell, John Mitchell, Pete Mitchell, Ralph Mitchell (alias Botkins and LeRoy Simson), Soloman Mithcell, Thomas Mitchell, Walter Mittlestadt, B. Mix, Elmo Mix, Claud A. Mizner, John Moate, Gabriel Moccasin, Floyd Mock, Robert Mock, Clarence E. Moe, Fred Moehle, E.A. Moeller, Fred Moffatt, Orville Moffet, Harvey Leroy Moffett Jr., Clarence Moffitt, Clayton Moffitt, Robert Winfield Mogren, William Mohan, Frank Molete, Joe Molinas, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 29/4)
    - Prisoner description cards: Albert Moline, Henry Molloy,William Molyneaux, Tim Monahan, Frank Monette, Nick Monno, E.J. Monohan, Joseph Monohan, Edward Monroe, Frank Monroe, Grinnell Monroe, Joe Monroe, Louis Monroe, Jens Monsen, Augustine Montano, Phillip Montano, Joe Monteau, Antonio Montes, Simon Montes, John Montesano, Coy Montgomery, Earl Montgomery, H.T. Montgomery, John P. Montgomery, Roy Montgomery, Louis Montrose, Louis Monts, Adrian Eugene Moody, Charles Bradley Moody, Lemuel Moody, Norman Felix Moody, Paul Moody, Vaudie Moody, Everett Moon, John Mooney, John P. Mooney, Lawrence J. Mooney, A.C. Moore, A.E. Moore, Allen W. Moore, Arthur Moore, Boyd Moore, Chester Moore, Chester A. Moore, Chris C. Moore, Christopher Charles Moore, Ed Moore, Frank C. Moore, George Moore, Hazel Moore, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Prisoner description cards: Howard Moore, Howard L. Moore, J.C. Moore, James Robert Moore, James Moore, James F. Moore, Jess Moore, John Ralph Moore, Joseph Moore, Kenneth Moore, Leroy Moore, Leslie Moore Jr., M.C. Moore, Ray Moore, Robert Moore (True name Alex W. Gradwohl), Roy Moore, Samuel Moore, Thomas Moore, W.D. Moore, W.F. Moore, Walter Moore, William Moore, Ace Moorehouse, Charles Moquist, Jim Moraco, Jesus Morales, Joe Morales, Ricardo Moralez, Joe Moralis, C.F. Moran, Charles H. Moran, Chrismas Moran, Clerence F. Moran, Clarence Frederick Moran, Frances E. Moran, Frank Moran, James W. Moran, James Moran, Matthew Moran, Robert Moran, Michael Morawski, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 29/6)
    - Prisoner description cards: W. Frederick Morden, Orille Cleo Morehouse, William Morelli, Tony Morello, F. Moreno, Francisco Moreno, Edward Lee Morey, George Morey, Ben Morgan, Charles Morgan, D.C. Morgan, Dave Morgan, Elva Morgan, Eugene Morgan, Fay Morgan, Frank Morgan, George Morgan, Harry Morgan, Harry Morgan, Harry Morgan, Haymond Lee Morgan, Henry Morgan, Jack Morgan, James Morgan, James Morgan, John Morgan, Joseph Morgan, Laura Morgan, Lewis Morgan, Lewis Morgan, Pete Morgan, Ray Morgan, Roy Morgan, Sam Morgan (Changed to Roy Deoss), Tex Morgan, Thomas Morgan, Wilber Morgan, Forest Morigeau, Francis Morin, Romeo Morin, Sargent Morin, Harry J. Morison, Orville Mork, Joe Morles, Victor Morlin, LeRoy Morningstar, Jack Moros, A.L. Morris, Abery Morris, Albert Morris, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Prisoner description cards: C.M. Morris, Charles Morris, David Morris, Edward Morris, Frank Morris, George Morris, J.C. Morris, James Morris, John Morris, Vernon Morris, William Morris, Dan J. Morrisey (alias A.F. McAlfree; J.B. Kenyon), James Morrisey, Cecil D. Morrison, Dan Morrison, E.G. Morrison, Eriel Morrison, John Morrison, John P. Morrison, Lawrence Morrison, Orin Morrison, Thomas Morrison, Arthur B. Morrow, Jack Morrow, Karl Morrow, Robert Morrow, Robert W. Morrow, Howard Morse, Robert Morse (alias Ralph Harmon), William Morse, Clarence Morsette, Lew Morsette, Winfred Morss, Walter Mort, JuDean Mortensen, Kairn Mortenson, Robert Ross Mortimer, Claud Morton, Earl Morton, Jess Morton, Thomas Morton, Joseph Mosbrucker, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 30/2)
    - Prisoner description cards: Claude Mosely, Arthur Moses, Luther Moses, Mountain Moses, Howard Mosley, Charles Mosney Jr., Joe Moson, Solomon Mosquito, Tomie Moss, George Motari, Leonard Motari, Leonard Motari (alias Frank L. Smith), Albert Motheral, Francis Mothershead, Joseph Moug, Eli Mougeau, Rose Marie Mountain Chief, Ed Mounts, Frank Mouser, William Mowall, Joseph Mowatt, Charles Moyer, Harley Moyer, Stanley Moyer, Chester A. Muck, Edward William Muehhausen, Alvin J. Mueller, Fred J. Mueller, Michael Mueller, Robert E. Muentener, John Muhleman, Neil Mulcaster, John W. Mulkey, M.J. Mullaney, Tom Mullen, Robert Mullenberg, Julius Muller, James Mulligan, Benjamin Mullins, William Mumford, Fernando Munaz, James Munden, James R. Munden, John Munden, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 30/3)
    - Prisoner description cards: Perry Munden, Jewel H. Mundt, Lee Muniz, Charlie Munn, Everett Clayton Munroe, Rollin J. Munroe, Joe Munski, Stanislaus Anthony Munski, Carl Munson, Thomas Muntain, Lester Munter, Tonosa Muntion, K. Murakami, Marvin Murdock, S.E. Murdock, S.E. Murdock, Henry Murell, Sebastian Murguia, A.H. Murphy, Bert Murphy, C.M. Murphy, Carol Murphy, Con Murphy, Dan Murphy, Dennis Murphy, Ed Murphy, Floyd Murphy, Frank Murphy, Frank Murphy, Harry Murphy, J.E. Murphy, J.F. Murphy, J.J. Murphy, Jack Murphy, James Murphy, James Murphy, Jim Murphy, Joe Murphy, John Murphy, John Murphy, John Murphy, John Murphy, John Ward Murphy, Joseph Murphy, Joseph Murphy, Leo J. Murphy, Robert Murphy, Roy Murphy, Thomas Murphy, Thomas J. Murphy, Thomas Murphy, Tom Murphy, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 30/4)
    - Prisoner description cards: V.J. Murphy (Virgil), William Murphy, William Patrick Murphy, William Murphy, Placida Murrada, Arthur Murray, C.C. Murray, C.C. Murray (alias Clyde Curtis Murray), E.L. Murray, Ed Murray, Frank Murray, George Norman Murray, Gilbert Murray, J.P. Murray, James Murray, James Murray, John Murray, John J. Murray, Joseph Murray, Martin Murray, Ralph Raymond Murray, Ray Murray, Roy Murray, Walter R. Murray, William Murray, B.E. Murrell, John Murrey, L.C. Murri, J.B. Music, Jesse B. Music, Sverre Muus, Charles E. Myer, Clarence R. Myers, D.F. Myers, Frank Myers, George Myers, George Myers, J.E. Myers (Jacob), James H. Myers, Leonard Myers, Montie Myers, O.E. Myers, Ray Myers, Ronald Irvine Myers, Thomas P. Myers, Walker Mack Myers (Walter), William Myers, Clarence Myhre, M.A. Myhre, Edward Fred Myers, Ernest G. Myrick, Audrey Myronic, Adolph Myrstal, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Prisoner description cards: Charles C. Naber, Joe Nadau, Alexander Nademovic, Gilbert Nadler, William Nafus, Charles Nagel, Donald Nagel, Andrew Nagle, John Nagy, James Kaguo Nakata, James Kangu Makata, Jim K. Nakata, Kazuo Nakata, Mike Nall, Frank Nams, Robert Nance, Ralph Nanini, Lawrence K. Nanoff, Tony J. Nardlli, Pete Narich, George or Norman Narman, Horace Nash, Robert A. Nash Jr., William Nason, William Jackson Nation, Raymond Alvin Naud, Earl Nault, Fred Nault, John Navalin (alias William Henderson), Ray Navarrio, Jofe Navarro (Jese), Jose Navarro, Edward Neal, Fred Neal, Harry R. Neal, W. Theodore Neal, William Neal, Richard Neary, Joseph Nedeau, S.T. Nedeau, Arthur Needham, Arthur Needham, Frank Needham, George Needy, Thomas Vern Neely, A. Neese (aliases Arthur neese; J.W. Bates and Chester A. Ness), Albert Neese, Leslie Howard Neff, Wayne Nefzger, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 30/6)
    - Prisoner description cards: Mike Negrete, John Nehl, Tony Neidamier, Neil Buckney, Charley Neil, John Neil, Frank Neill, Ray Neilson, Bernice Nelms, Alfred Nelson, Charles Nelson, Charles A. Nelson, Charles Nelson, Charles F. Nelson, Chris Nelson, Claire Nelson, Clarence Nelson, Clarence Nelson, Clarence Marvin Nelson, Dave Nelson, David Cooper Nelson, E.E.F. Nelson, E.W. Nelson, Earl Nelson, Earl Howard Nelson, Edward Nelson, Edward Nelson, Emmet Nelson, Frank Nelson, Fred Nelson, Gaylord Nelson, Gerald Nelson, Gerald Alvin Nelson, Gilbert Nelson, Glen Nelson, Gus Nelson, Harvey Nelson, Henry Nelson, Herbert Nelson, James Nelson, Joe Nelson, John Nelson, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Prisoner description cards: Kenneth Nelson, Leonard Nelson, Lewis Nelson, M.A. Nelson, Merton Nelson, Orvil E. Nelson, Oscar Nelson, Sylvester Nelson, Walter Nelson, William B. Nelson, William B. Nelson, J.A. Nelton, Simon Neria, John Nesbit, Sam J. Nesloney, Edward Netterberg, Clarence Neuman, Julius Neuman, Herbert Neumann, Rogelio Nevajar, Frank J. Nevills, William Nevins, Anthony H. Newberger, Patricia Newberger, Lester Newbern, Wayne Newbern, Charles Newbert, George Newby, George Newby, Ernest R. Newcomb, Harry Newcomb, Ralph Newcomb, Jack Newell, John Newell, Ray Newell, James D. Newland, Albert Newman, Floyd Newman, Guy Newman, Harry Newman, J.F. Newman, John Newman, John Newman, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Prisoner description cards: Louis R. Newman, Murphy Muriel Newman, Paul Newman, Ray Newman, William Newman, Louis Newrobe, Bertha Newsome, Jack Newsome, Charles B. Newton, Frank Newton, Frank Newton, Paul Newton, York New, Walter Niami, James Nicely (True name Jack Bowman), Robert Nichol, Frank Nichola, Martin Nicholas, W.H. Nicholas, Cecil Nichols, Dan Nichols (True name Charles Nichols), E.C. Nichols, Fred Nichols, Henry Nichols, Leon Fred Nichols, Richard Nichols, Ronald Nichols, Thomas Jeff Nichols, Walter Nichols, Frank Nicholson, James W. Nicholson Jr., Clarence Nickerson, Thomas Nickola, Alexander Nickolson, Frank Nicolai, Frank Nicolai, Frank Nicolai, George Nicolof, Clarence Nielsen, F.C. Nielson, Richard Nielson, Henry Nieman, Paul Nieman, R.D. Nightingale, Paul Nitchie, John Niva, Harry Njos, Burns Nobiles, Floyd Noble, Horace Noble, Troy Noble, William Noble, William Noble, John Edward Nodine, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Prisoner description cards: George Noel, Joe Noel, William R. Noggle, Philip Nokes, Frank Nolan, James Nolan (True name Dan Carroll alias Jack Blaine, Paul Nolan, Robert Nolan, Thomas Nolan, William Nolan, Jack Noland, Ben Noll, Joe Noll, Henry Nomee, Philip No More Tobacco, Griff Noon, John Noonan, Fred Nopen, Adolph Norby, Albert Norby, Leo Norby, William Norby, Elver Norcutt, Ole Nordall, George Nordby, R.J. Nordgulen, John Nordman, Robert Nordstrom, Ed Norling, George Norman, Gus Norman, Harry Norman, Henry Norman, Judson Norman, Lonnie Charles Norman, Pete Norman, Joe Norquay, John Norquay, Charles J. Norren, Charles Norris, Ernest M. Norris, G.E. Norris, Garnet Earl Norris, Harold G. Norris, Henry Norris, John North, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 31/4)
    - Prisoner description cards: John Northrop, Ed Norton, Everett Norton, Glen Norton, James Norton, Keith Norton, Pat Norton, Steve H. Norton, Thomas Norton, William Nortske, Clarence Norville, Clarence Norville, John Notte, John Novotne, Joseph G. Nowatney, Ray D. Noyd, Richard Nrucas (True name Richard Payne alias Richard Steward Gean Babtist), William Nuhring, Chester Nulliner, George Nulliner, Chester Nulliner, Burel Nunn, Elmer Nunnelley, Lynn M. Nye, William Nye (alias C.D. Platt; J.F. Adams; J. Rolf), Gustav E. Nygren, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Prisoner description cards: Charles Oakes, Roy Oakes, Ernest Oates, Frank O'Black, Peter Obaradovich, Patrick O'Brady, Michael O'Brian, Donald O'Brien, Frank O'Brien, Fred O'Brien, James F. O'Brien, James O'Brien, Jimmy O'Brien, John O'Brien, Larry O'Brien, Mayne O'Brien (True name Ida Nelson), Micheal O'Brien, Pat O'Brien, Raymond O'Brien, Robert E. O'Brien, Ruth O'Brien, Thomas O'Brien, Tom O'Brien, William O'Brien, William O'Brien, William F. O'Brien, William J. O'Brien, John O'Bryan (alias Haveder; H. William), Thomas O'Bryne, Vincent Paster Garcia Ocasio, Ben Ochsner, Elizabeth Ocker, Floyd Ocker, Robert O'Connell, Thomas Joseph O'Connell, Thomas Joseph O'Connell, Norman O'Conner, Daniel O'Connor, E.D. O'Connor, Earl D. O'Connor (Dunlap), Earl D. O'Connor, Eddie O'Connor, Frank O'Connor, Jack O'Connor (alias Jack Slade; Henry O'Connor and W.J. Slade; true name Wyatt J. Slade), Jack O'Connor, James O'Connor, James O'Connor, James O'Connor, M.J. O'Connor (alias James W. Baldwin and James Willis Baldwin), Tom O'Connor, Tom O'Connor, Walter O'Connor, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 31/6)
    - Prisoner description cards: John E. O'Connors, F. Odaw, Thomas O'Day, Charles O. O'Dell, James O'Dell, Lyle J. O'Dell, Samuel Lawson O'Dell, Charles Odenwald, Wallace Odneal, Ed O'Donnell, Jim O'Donnell, John A. O'Donnell, Patrick O'Donnell, Terrance O'Donnell, William O'Donnell, Ernest Offerdahl, A.E. Ogden, Ervan Lee Ogden, William Ogg, Nels Ogland, Albert Ogle, James Ogle, Heber O'Green, Floyd O'Hara, Frank O'Hara, Jessie O'Hara, Terry O'Hara, Thomas J. O'Hara, Grant O'Harrah, L.J. O'Keefe, Michael O'Keefe, Arthur J. O'Kelley, John O'Kelley, Floyd O'Kelly, William A. Okruta, Antony Olaque, Tim O'Larey, Tim O'Lary, Fred Olbo, Maurice Oldaker, Francis Old Horn, John O'Leary, Mikail Dee O'Leary, Tim O'Leary, Fred F. Olen, Harry Oleson, Arthur W. Olive, Clyde Oliver, James D. Oliver, John Oliver, Richard Oliver, Archie Olmstead, James Olmstead, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Prisoner description cards: Leslie Olmstead, Nova Leslie Olmstead, Reuben Olmstead, John O'Loughlin, Al Olsen, Clifford Olsen, Henry Olsen, Leonard C. Olsen, Robert L. Olsen, William Olsen, A.N. Olson, Alvin Olson, Arnold Olson, Carl Olson, Charles L. Olson, Clifford Olson, Clifford Olson, David Arnold Olson, Earl Olson, Ed Olson, Ed Olson, Ed Olson, Edward Olson, Edward Joseph Olson, Elmer Olson, Edward Floyd Olson, Fred Olson, Goodman Olson, Gus Olson, Hans Olson, Harry Olson, John Olson, Joseph Olson, Joseph Olson (alias Joe Stone), Louis Olson, Marvin M. Olson, Olaf Olson, Oscar M. Olson, Pete Olson, Ray Olson, Clarence M. Olstad, Matt Olstrom, James O'Malley, J.J. O'Malley, Peter O'Malley, William O'Malley, Alfred Omisto, Charles O'Neale, Ernest O'Neil, James O'Neil, Lyle O'Neil, Barney O'Neill, Charles H. O'Neill, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Prisoner description cards: Frank O'Neill, Harry O'Neill (alias Harry Hurstad and Buckney O'Neill), Hugh John O'Neill, James H. O'Neill, James O'Neill, Joseph O'Neill, Charles Ong, Michael E. Onufer, Chris Opsel, Harry Orcutt, John O'Reilly, Terrance O'Reilly, Thomas O'Reilly, Pete Orescanin, Thomas B. O'Riley Jr., Paul Orlando, John Orloff, George Orlovich, Brenirlaw Orlowski (alias Tom Arlow), Frank Orosz, Protancio Orozco, Eugene Orr, Louis Ortice, Joe Ortiz, Fred W. Orton, William Orton, Earl Edward Osborn, Alfred J. Osborne, Charles Osborne, Arnold J. Oschenbrenner, Frank Osgood, Daniel O'Shea, Drummond Osseman, K.M. Osswald, Josephy Ostman, Richard Oswald, Julius Otonochar, George H. Ott, Mike Ott, Benjamin H. Ottenstror, Clarence Ouelette, Cyr Ouellett, Emil Ouelette, Lawrence Ouellette, Edward Oulette, Lawrence Oulette, Alma Ovard, B.B. Overall, Art Overby, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 32/3)
    - Prisoner description cards: Albert Overturf, Ralph Thomas Owen, Raymond T. Owen, Raymond T. Owen, Z.T. Owen, Charles Owens, D.H. Owens, Daniel Owens, Herman M. Owens, James Thorpe Owens, Kenneth Owens, Nelson Owens, W.V. Owens, Wade Owens, Archibald P. Owings, Albert Oxford, Watson M. Oyler, Sam Paakanen, Merlyn Pace, Marie Pacheco, Martin Pachero, Robert Pachett, G.D. Packard, Thomas Packhan, Richard Wilson Packineau, Irvin Paddock, M.N. Paddock, Elias Padilla, John Padilla, Joe Padillo, Jack Page, Orville Page, John Pahlke, V.H. Paige, Edgar Paillett, Henry Painter, Samuel Palama, Frank Palffy, Jack Palm, Wallace Palm, Bud Palmer, F.R. Palmer, Earl Palmer (aliases Rayfield Carter; Malvin Carter; Elmer Love and Jack Brown), George C.W. Palmer, George Palmer, George D. Palmer, Harry Palmer, Hugh Palmer, J.C. Palmer, James E. Palmer, Leo W. Palmer, William Palmer, William Fred Palmer, Will Palmer,Salvatori Palmo, Lorenzo M. Panalez, Peter Panasa, John C. Pancake, Egbert Pandolfo, Nicolas Panegura, Caesar Panerio, Albert Panicco, Tony Panion, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Prisoner description cards: Nick Pantelich, Savas Pantelides, Nick Papas, Madison J. Pape, Madison J. Pape, Angelo Papillo, Ulysses Papp, George Papparumpus (alias George Papaus), Chris Pappas, Frank Pappas, Steve Pappas, William G. Pappas, Donet Paquette, Frank Pauanteau, Daniel Parce, Daniel Parce, Donaciano Paredez, Charles Parent, Thomas Parenteau, Andrew Paris, Gust Paris, Fred Pariseau, Fred Parizeau, William Parizeau, William Parizeau, William A. Parizeau, Harry Park, Harold K. Parke, A.L. Parker, Arthur Parker, Bert Parker, Daniel Parker, Ed Parker, Jack Parker, Jasper Parker, Jess Parker, Johna Parker, Leroy Parker, Marion O'Neill Parker, Thomas Parkins, Eugene Parks, George Parks, Harry Parks, Robert Parks, William A. Parks, Jess William Parlow, Arvan H. Parnell, Manuel R. Paroda, Clifton Parr, Jess Parr, Francisco Sactillo Parra, Martin Parrent, Jim Parris, Clifford Parrish, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Prisoner description cards: Jack Partee, William Parsons, Sanford Parsons, James Parsons, Harold Parson, Alvin A. Parshall, Frank Parrlich, Joseph Parrison, Joe Parrish, John D. Partlow, Lowis Partridge, Leon Pase, J. P. Pask, John Pask, G.C. Pasley, Vasile Paso, Edward J. Patalas, Eugene Patneaude, LaRue Patnode, Hubert Patrick, Hubert Patrick, Lazell Patrick, Lazell W. Patrick, Charles Edward Patterson, Ed Patterson, James Franklyn Patterson, John Patterson, John Patterson, M.L. Patterson, Morley B. Patterson, Oscar C. Patterson, Pat Patterson, Robert Felix Patterson, William Patterson, William Patterson, George E. Pattibone, Mike Pattkovich, Robert G. Patton, Thomas Patton, Andrew Paul, Ben Paul (alias Ben LaFontain; Ben LaFountain and Jack Benjamin Paul), Edward Paul, Frank Paul, George Paul, John Paul, Rene Paul, Robert Paul, Tony Paul (True name is Tony Palucky), Warren B. Paul, Warren B. Paul, Andros Paulos, Ole Paulson, Martin Pavich, Nick Pavich, John Pavie, Gurrimo Pavoreal, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - Prisoner description cards: Cornelio Payan, Melvin Payette, Birdsell Payne, Dave Payne, William H. Payne, William Payton, Ervin H. Peacock, Walter Franklin Pearl, B.E. Pearson, Edgar Pearson, Ervin Pearson, Frederick Pearson, Joseph Pearson, R.E. Pearson, Thomas Pearson, Jerry Pecore (alias Jerry Stevens), B.E. Pederson, Ben E. Pederson, Gordon Lloyd Pederson, Pedro Pedilla, Robert Peeler, Frank Peelman, Leroy Peerboom, John R. Peers, Harry Peet, Sam Peevey, Joe Pelchie, Joe Pelchie, Joseph Pelchie, Leon Pelee, Jack Arthur Pelesky, W.H. Pelham, Herman Pelke, Porter A. Pelkey, Andy Pellitier, Frank Pellizari, Ben E. Pelchie, Joe Peltchie, Ray Peltier, A.T. Pemberton, Bob Pemberton, Earl L. Pemberton, William Pembroke, Cruz Penaloza, William C. Pendercraft, William Pendergast, Earl Pendry, Earl H. Pendry, William Pendy, Judson H. Pennabaker, John A. Pennington, Robert R. Pennington, Earl Clifford Penstrom, John O. Pentz, Albert Peoples, James Pephyr, E.J. Pepin, Vince Pepion, Jane Perach, Carlos Perales, Willie Percy, Joe Perez, Ruben Perez, Teranquileon Perez, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 33/1)
    - Prisoner description cards: Glenn Pergande, Harry N. Perham, Eli Perio, Calvin Perkins, Charles Perkins, Francis M. Perkins, Joseph Perkins, William James Perkins, William James Perkins, Harry Permeau, Peter Pernicke, Constance Pernot, Constance Pernot, Lester Perrin, Orval Perring, Orville Perring, James Perrington, A.V. Perry, Alex, C.A. Perry, Charles J. Perry, George Perry, John Perry, Joseph Perry, L.H. Perry, Taylor Perryman, Geno Perso, Herman Person, William Perue, Paul Pesanti, Pasquale Pescuzzi, James Petel, Franklin G. Peterkin, Carl Peters, Carl Peters, Donald Peters, Earl Peters, Frank Peters, Isaac Peters, Joseph Peters (alias Joe Stephens and J.W. Smith, Ralph Peters, Ralph Stanley Peters, Raynen W. Petersen, A.H. Peterson, Albert J. Peterson, August Peterson, Carl O. Peterson, Christian Peterson, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Prisoner description cards: Curtis Peterson, Donald James Peterson, E.E. Peterson, Eben Peterson, Frank Peterson, George W. Peterson, Gerald Peterson, Hans Peterson, Harry Peterson, Harold Peterson, Harold R. Peterson, John Peterson, John Merrit Peterson, L.B. Peterson, Louis Peterson, Otto Peterson, Raymond Peterson, Raymond P. Peterson, Richard E. Peterson, Robert Lee Peterson, Robert Peterson, Roy Peterson, Swan Peterson, William Peterson, William E. Peterson, William Peterson, William Peterson, Herbert Petet, Jack Petetin, Richard Pethick, I.C. Petrie, Mike Petrillo, Robert Frank Petronek, Herman Petros, Joseph Petroski, Donald Gilbert Petrowski, George Pettibone, John F. Pettitt,Sever Petto, Abel Pettokangus, Eugene Pettus, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 33/3)
    - Prisoner description cards: Jack Petty, Raymond B. Pfeifer, Frank Pfrimmer, Leo Phalen, Arthur Phares, Arthur Phelps, Dan Phelps, Ernest Phelps, Francis Phelps, Talbert Phelps, William Phelps, William Phelps, Wendle P. Philamlee Jr., Jack Philbrick, Albert Philips, Joe Steven Phillippi, Archie L. Phillips, Buck Charles Phillips, C.W. Phillips, Carleton Phillips, Charles Phillips, Elbert V. Phillips, Eugene Phillips, Eugene Wents Phillips, Frank Phillips, George Phillips, Harold Phillips, Jack Phillips, John A. Phillips, L.R. Phillips, Laverne Phillips, Mary E. Phillips, Melvin Phillips, O.F. Phillips, Owen Phillips, V.E. Phillips, Wilbur Phillips, William Harold Phillips, Taivs Philman, Joe Phipps, Jimmy Piano, Peter Pazzola, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Prisoner description cards: J.A. Picard, Eddie Pichette, Eddie Pichette, Mike Pichette, Narcisse Pichette, Narcissi Pichette, Kenneth F. Pickett, Richard Pickett, Clifford Pidcock, Steve Pienovich, Albert L. Pierce, Chester Pierce, Ed Pierce, Edward Pierce, Edwin Pierce, Elmer Pierce, F.H. Pierce, George Pierce, John Byron Pierce, Lambert Pierce, Ray S. Pierce, Waldo Pierce, Archie Piercy, F.H. Piercy, James Piermont, Patrick Pierre, Jack L. Pierrie, Clyde Pierson, Frank Pierson, George Pierson, Rayburn Pierson, Arnold Pietila, George Pietsch, John Pilch, Gilbert Pilcher, Ray Pilkington, George Pilipovich, Harris Pilley, Earl Pillsbury, Robert F. Pilz, Sestena Pina, Harland Ping, Lee Ping, Lee Ping, Wright Hale Pinkham, Fred Pinnow, Frank A. Pinson, Marvin Otis Pipes, Walter Pipinich, Walter Pipinich, Paul Pippenger, Pellegro Pippi, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 33/5)